Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Addendum, 1910-1955; 313165
  - Publicity, 1941-1955; 313190 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Rand School - Descriptions, 1919, undated; 313192 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Rand School - Descriptions, undated, 1930-1939; 313312 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Rand School High School, 1935-1936, undated; 313313 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Rand School Relations with Labor Unions, undated, 1924-1948; 313315 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Research Department and Committee, undated; 313316 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Save the People's House, 1933; 313317 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Save the People's House - Socialist Party's Responses, undated, 1933; 313318 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Stag Dinners/Theatre Parties, 1933; 313319 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee, 1946-1947; 313320 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Student Enrollment, 1933, undated; 313193 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Students Examination, undated; 313321 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Students Information, undated, 1938-1947; 313322 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Summer School, undated, 1932-1936; 313323 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Taft-Hartley Law, undated, 1947; 313324 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Tax Exemption, 1939-1954; 313325 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Tax Exemptions/IRS, 1947, 1950-1954; 313194 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Tchernavin, Tatiana Lecture: "Escape from the Soviets", 1934-1935; 313326 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Trade Union Institute, 1934-1947, undated; 313327 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Bills, 1954-1955; 313328 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - War Bond Rally, 1942; 313329 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee, 1930s; 313330 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1941-1942; 313331 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Youth Forum, 1946, undated; 313332 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Unprocessed photographs (Box 71)
- Series VIII: Fragile Originals, undated; 315504
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 22, 317393 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 23, 317394 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 24, 317395 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 25, 317396 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 26, 317397 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 27, 317398 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 28, 317399 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 29, 317400 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 30, 317401 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 31, 317402 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 32, 317403 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 33, 317404 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 34, 317405 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 35, 317406 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 36, 317407 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 37, 317408 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 39, 317409 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 40, 317410 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 41, 317411 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 43, 317412 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 44, 317413 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 46, 317414 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 1 through Box 1, Folder 3, 315505 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 5 through Box 1, Folder 6, 315506 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 7 through Box 1, Folder 8, 315507 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 9 through Box 2, Folder 1, 315508 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 2, Folder 3 through Box 2, Folder 12, 315509 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 2, Folder 18 through Box 3, Folder 1, 315510 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 3, Folder 2 through Box 3, Folder 9, 315575 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 3, Folder 10 through Box 4, Folder 2, 316063 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 4, Folder 3 through Box 4, Folder 36, 316100 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 5, Folder 5 through Box 5, Folder 15, 316239 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 6, Folder 1 through Box 6, Folder 20, 316291 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 7, Folder 7 through Box 7, Folder 26, 317464 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 8, Folder 1 through Box 8, Folder 10, 317469 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 9, Folder 1 through Box 9, Folder 12, 317798 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 10, Folder 1 through Box 10, Folder 13, 317799 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 11, Folder 1 through Box 11, Folder 10, 317837 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 12, Folder 1 through Box 12, Folder 15, 317974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 13, Folder 1 through Box 13, Folder 21, 317975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 14, Folder 1 through Box 15, Folder 20, 318060 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 1 through Box 16, Folder 20, 318301 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 17, Folder 5 through Box 19, Folder 15, 318906 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 20, Folder 2 through Box 20, Folder 16, 319040 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 21, Folder 1 through Box 23, Folder 12, 319041 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 24, Folder 2 through Box 25, Folder 13, 319144 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 26, Folder 1 through Box 26, Folder 14, 319145 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 27, Folder 2 through Box 27, Folder 16, 319233 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 2 through Box 28, Folder 16, 319234 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 1 through Box 29, Folder 13, 319235 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folders 2 through 9, 346632 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10, 346633 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10, 346634 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10, 346635 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 11, 346636 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folders 12 through 15, 346637 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 16 and Box 60, Folder 1, 346638 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 1 and 2, 346639 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 2, 346640 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3, 346641 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3, 346642 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3, 346643 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 3 through 6, 346644 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 6, 346645 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 6 through 8, 346646 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 61, Folders 1 through 3, 346647 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 61, Folders 4 through 10, 346648 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 1 through 4, 346649 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 5 through 9, 346650 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 10 through 12, 346651 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 13 through 14, 346652 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 1 through 2, 346654 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 3 through 5, 346655 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals From Box 63, Folder 6, 346656 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 7 through 8, 346657 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 9 through 14, 346658 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Oversize Photographs: portraits, group photos, dinner event photos, 1937-1942; undated (Box Shared Tamiment 006, Folder 9-10)
  - British Labor Exhibit photographs, undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Series IX: Embossing Stamp, undated; 2013.039; 480238
  - Rand School Embossing Stamp, unknown; 2013.039; 480239 (Box 70)